JOHNNY DUNN

https://github.com/jddunn/ | https://jddunn.github.io/ | johnnyddunn@gmail.com

Summary

Full-stack dev experienced in building machine learning infrastructure / data pipelines, training custom models, and fine-tuning LLMs. Experienced in web3 / full-cycle smart contract development, governance / DAOs, MEV bots, and NFT integrations in web and games.

Professional Experience

Senior Blockchain Engineer

Tilting Point New York, NY

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

- Acted as blockchain architect to build infrastructure and marketplace backend for NFTs, and token and NFT integrations in mobile games SDKs on Polygon / MATIC chain, consulting with MATIC engineers for best practices.
- Developed ERC-20 and ERC-721 smart contracts with custom metadata properties, APIs for managing NFT metadata, blockchain indexing microservices for transaction events, and an internal airdropping service. Architected secure multisig wallet operations; rescued \$1 million+ in MATIC from missent transactions.

New York, NY <u>eBay</u>

Software Engineer 2 (Full-Stack)

June 2020 - April 2021

- Worked on REST API in Scala & Spring-Boot to service data asynchronously based on item selections to UI, improving UX.
- Created deployment infrastructure enabling E2E developer experience for backend / ML teams. Set up Jenkins pipelines to connect underlying UI libraries, SSR backends to serve web data, and APIs returning ads data from ML models.

Freelance (Grapple Media, Notebrush, Edelman, HAL)

New York, NY

NLP Engineer / Software Engineer / Product Designer (Contract)

November 2018 - Jan 2021

- Created user stories, animated wireframes and functional product demo for Notebrush's MVP.
- Developed web crawling infrastructure with automated pipeline to feed data into training news classifiers and sentiment analysis models for Grapple Media. Created a recommendation system for news stories.
- Trained models to create photo filters applying aesthetics of specific films to selfies for Edelman's interactive AI exhibits.
- Sold sentiment analysis model and dataset to HAL (HereAfterLegacy), and continued development work to deliver their MVP.

IPSoft Cognitive Implementation Engineer

June 2017 - December 2017

- Implemented modules for virtual assistant AI Amelia for corporate client-facing solutions following agile practices.
- Improved workflow and productivity by writing data processing scripts to be distributed to internal teams.

Projects

Quire.work - Turn static forms and interviews into conversational experiences powered by LLMs. 2023 https://quire.work

Restless - Always-on anti-malware software using malicious language processing (HAN model) techniques. 2020 https://github.com/jddunn/restless

Text RPG Engine - ES6 JS library to create text adventures / interactive fiction with custom player interactions. 2020 https://github.com/iddunn/text-rpg-engine

Dementia progression analysis - Dementia progression classifier for MRIs using CNN and transfer learning. 2018 https://github.com/iddunn/dementia-progression-analysis

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Design and Technology (May 2017) - Parsons School of Design

Awards

5th Place, AT&T National VR and AR Challenge, with THiNKIMMERSIVE team. (http://npe100.com/)

2017

XRC Labs Young Entrepreneurs Residential Program

Spring 2017

Skills

Programming Languages	Solidity Python Go / Golang JavaScript TypeScript Java Scala C# SQL HTML CSS
Frontend	React Next.js Redux Toolkit (RTK) ChakraUl NextUl Tailwind D3.js three.js SCSS
Backend	ethers.js HardHat LangChain Hugging Face OpenAl FastAPI Django Tornado Keras TensorFlow PyTorch OpenCV spaCy CoreNLP NumPy SciPy pandas scikit-learn Celery Scrapy BS4 Selenium Flashbots Geth Gnosis Safe
Databases	MySQL Postgres Prisma SQLAlchemy MongoDB DynamoDB GraphQL Hadoop Kafka Elasticsearch Redis
DevOps	AWS (EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, Amplify, RedShift) Docker Kubernetes Jenkins
Tools / Software / Other	Unity Git Postman Linux Burp Suite Adobe Creative Suite Processing openFrameworks SketchUp PyCharm IntelliJ Visual Studio PWAs Electron Capacitor Android Studio